안녕하세요
Hello.
쉘든 쿠퍼 박사입니다
I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
'쉘든과 깃발 배우기'의
첫 회를 시청하고 계십니다
and welcome to
the premiere episode
of Sheldon Cooper Presents:
Fun with Flags.
앞으로 52주 동안
저와 함께 기학을 공부해보죠
Over the next 52 weeks,
you and I are going to explore
the dynamic world
of vexillology.
쿠퍼 박사님,
잠깐만요
Hang on, Dr. C.
기학은 뭔가요?
What's vexillology?
기학은 깃발을
다루는 학문입니다
Vexillology is
the study of flags.
멋지네요
Cool.
방금 뭔가 배운 것 같아요
I think I just
learned something.
재밌었나요?
Did you have fun doing it?
물론이죠
I'll say.
이 비디오 팟캐스트는
재미와 정보를 모두 제공합니다
Fun and information are two
sides to this video podcast,
양면이 다른
깃발처럼 말이에요
not unlike the only
two-sided state flag--
오레곤
Oregon.
이것 보세요
Oh, look.
안녕, 미스터 비버
Hello, Mr. Beaver.
다음 에피소드에는
모두의 궁금증을 풀어드립니다
In future episodes, we'll answer
some burning questions:
직사각형 모양이
아닌 깃발은?
What's the only
non-rectangular flag?
깃발에 제일 많이
등장하는 동물은?
What animal appears
most often on flags?
두번째로 제일 많이
등장하는 동물은?
What animal appears second
most often on flags?
여러가지를 준비했어요
And more.
짱!
Sweet!
왜 백기를 흔드시나요?
Why are you waving
a white flag?
항복하는 거죠
I'm surrendering...
너무 재밌어서요
to fun.
(laughs)
오늘 에피소드는
재밌지는 않지만
Now, today's episode of
Fun with Flags is not fun,
매우 중요합니다
but it is important.
깃발을 잡는 법과
"Flags: you gotta know
how to hold 'em,
접는 법에 대해
배워봅시다
you gotta know
how to fold 'em."
우선 깃발의
각 부분을 살펴보죠
Let's start by identifying
the parts of our flag.
깃대에 가까운 부분을
호이스트라고 부릅니다
This edge is the hoist,
and it's used to...
실례할게
Excuse me,
sorry, excuse me.
컷
Cut.
촬영 중인 거 안 보여?
Did you not see
we are rolling?
미안, 페니랑
저녁 약속이 있어서
Sorry. I'm having dinner
with Penny.
지금 나가야 해
I have to get out of here.
나한테는 깃발에
대한 지식이 있는데
And I have flag knowledge
꼭 내보내야 한다고
that I have to
get out of here!
(sighs)
괜찮아?
You okay?
아니, 살짝 짜증이 나네
No, I'm a little rattled.
그래도 포트 섬터의
깃발처럼 아직 펄럭이고 있어
But like the flag over
Fort Sumter, I'm still here.
테이크 투
And... take two.
안녕하세요
Hello.
쉘든 쿠퍼 박사입니다
I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
'쉘든과 깃발 배우기'의
첫 회를 시청하고 계십니다
and welcome to
the premiere episode
of Sheldon Cooper Presents:
Fun with Flags.
앞으로 52주 동안
저와 함께 기학을 공부해보죠
Over the next 52 weeks,
you and I are going to explore
the dynamic world
of vexillology.
쿠퍼 박사님,
잠깐만요
Hang on, Dr. Cooper.
기학은 뭔가요?
What's vexillology?
기학은...
Vexillology is...
깃발에 얼굴은
왜 그렸어?
why is there a face
on that flag?
퍼디난드 T. 깃발이야
It's Ferdinand T. Flag.
젊은 시청자를
끌어들이려고
I thought he might help bring in
some younger viewers.
그렇군
Confound it!
훌륭한 생각이야,
처음부터 다시 하자
You're right, it's brilliant.
Let's take it from the top.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x14
The Beta Test Initiation
Original Air Date on January 26, 2012
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
정말 즐거운 시간이었다
That was a really
nice dinner.
이렇게 불러줘서 고마워
I'm glad you asked me
out again.
나도,
그리웠어
Me, too; I missed you.
매일 보는데 뭘
You see me all the time.
섹스가 그리운게 아니고?
You sure you just
don't miss the sex?
너랑 하는 섹스는
환상적이거든
Well, yeah, sex with you
is pretty great.
해본 적 있어?
Have you ever tried it?
해봤지
I have.
네 말이 맞아
You are not wrong.
다시 데이트를 한다면
I just think if we're
gonna try dating again,
진도를 천천히
하면 좋겠어
we should take things slow.
그런 거라면
난 자신 있어
Oh, I can take it slow.
고등학교 때
첫 여자친구 캐런 알아?
Did I ever tell you
about my first girlfriend
in high school,
Karen Berberick?
지금까지도 우리가
사귀었던걸 모르더라
To this day she doesn't know
we were going out.
덕분에 헤어질 때는
좀 수월했지만
Made it easier on her
when I broke things off.
그렇게까지 느릴
필요는 없어
Okay, well, maybe
not that slow.
이러면 어때
How about this,
컴퓨터 소프트웨어의
개발 절차에 대해 알고 있나?
are you familiar with
the typical development
for computer software?
재미를 위해
모른다고 할게
You know, just for fun,
let's say I'm not.
프로그램이 배포되기 전에
Before an application
is released,
시범 운영을 하지
they give it a trial run.
우리도 그러면 되지
W-We could do that.
잘 안 풀리면
화를 내지 말고
And if we hit a rough spot,
instead of getting mad,
'앗, 버그를 발견했다'
just say, "Hey, we found a bug,"
문제점을 보고하고
고쳐나가는 거야
and we report it
so it can be fixed.
베타 테스트처럼?
You mean like a beta test?
정확히 말하자면
알파 테스트야
Well, technically,
this would be an alpha test.
베타 테스트는 개발에
참여하지 않은 사람들이...
A beta test requires people
that weren't involved
in the development
of the appli...
베타 테스트를 아는 것
자체가 대단하지 않아?
Seriously, do I not get credit
for knowing beta test?
응, 그렇지
No, you should.
물론이지
Absolutely.
내가 너무
아는 척 했다
That was me being pedantic.
우리의 첫 버그였어
That's our first bug.
네가 보고를 했으니
You reported it.
난 고칠 수 있어
I can fix that.
봤지?
이건 효과가 좋다고
See? This is good.
그래
All right.
한번 해보자
Let's give it a shot.
서로 리스트를 작성하고
Great. You keep a list,
I'll keep a list.
나중에 교환하자
At some point, we'll exchange.
알았어
Okay.
- 잘자, 레너드
- 잘자
- Good night, Leonard.
- Night.
좋았어, 호프스태더
Attaboy, Hofstadter.
소프트웨어 개발에 비유하면
퍽이나 좋아하겠다
Nothing gets the ladies hotter
than software development
analogies.
돌아왔다
Hey, I'm back.
컷
SHELDON:
Cut.
테이크 47
(sighs)
Take 47.
깃발에 대해
재밌는 사실이 있어
Here's an interesting
fact about flags.
어디 한번 들어보자
I will take that action.
리히텐슈타인과 아이티
깃발이 같은 건 우연이래
The flags
of Liechtenstein and Haiti
were identical by coincidence,
1936년 올림픽에서 서로
경쟁하기 전까지는 몰랐대
a fact that wasn't discovered
until they competed
against each other
at the 1936 Olympics.
다행인 것은
And thankfully,
그 시기에 파시즘이
대두되면서 덜 주목받았어
their embarrassment
was overshadowed
by the rise of Fascism.
새 휴대폰 좀 볼까
Let's see the new phone.
출근길에 하나 샀어
I stopped on the way to work.
나랑 같이 비닐 벗길래?
Hey, do you want to peel
the plastic off with me?
정말?
Really?
내가?
Me?
그게 제일 짜릿한
순간이잖아
That's, like, the best part.
한쪽 잡아
Grab a corner.
(chuckles)
카우보이,
뭐가 그렇게 급해?
Whoa, what's your
hurry, cowboy?
이 순간을 즐기자
Savor the moment.
Oh, yeah.
카우보이 얘기가
나와서 그런데
Speaking of cowboys,
소가 두 마리 그려진
깃발이 어느 나라인지 알아?
do you know what country has not
one but two cows on its flag?
'안도라'라는 작은 내륙국이야
The tiny
landlocked nation of Andorra.
다음 에피소드가
절로 써지는구나
Oh, the next classic episode
of Sheldon Cooper Presents:
Fun with Flags
is writing itself.
음성 인식 좀 해볼게
Oh, let me try
the voice recognition.
비닐도 벗기게 해줬는데
너무 욕심 내지 마
Hey, I let you peel the plastic,
don't get greedy.
헬로?
(chimes)
Hello?
헬로
(chimes)
SIRI: Hello.
이름이 뭐죠?
(chimes)
What's your name?
제 이름은 시리입니다
(chimes)
My name? It's Siri.
잘됐다
(chuckling)
Look at that.
드디어 너도
여자랑 대화할 수 있네
There's finally a woman in
your life you can talk to.
싱글이신가요?
(chimes)
Are you single?
결혼을 하지는
않았습니다
(chimes)
I don't have a marital status,
맞게 대답했는지
모르겠네요
if that's what you're asking.
너무 개인적인
질문이였나봐요
Yeah, you're right,
that's too personal.
아직 잘 모르는 사이인데
We hardly know each other.
(chimes)
커피나 한 잔 할까요?
How about a cup of coffee?
커피숍 6개를
찾았습니다
(chimes)
I've found six coffee shops.
그 중 3곳이
근처에 있습니다
Three of them
are fairly close to you.
이따 보자
I will see you
gentlemen later.
또 상처받겠네
(exhales)
She is gonna break his heart.
(ethereal music plays on TV)
시간과 공간을 넘나드는
기계를 가졌는데도
For someone
who has a machine
that can travel anywhere
in time and space,
닥터후는 현재의 런던에만
머물어서 아쉽네
Doctor Who sure does have
a thing for modern-day London.
계속 그렇게 떠들면
Careful, it's that kind of sass
올해 닥터후 컨벤션에
초대받지 못할 수 있어
that can get a person uninvited
to this year's Who Con.
이건 데이트로
치는 거 아니지?
Uh, we're not counting
this as a date,
are we?
잘 모르겠는데
Um, I'm not sure,
아니라고 해야 맞지?
but I think the right
answer here is "no."
버그를 발견했어,
남자가 시간을 보내자 하면
Bug report: When a guy asks me
to spend time with him,
집에서 TV를 보는 것 보단
재밌는 데이트를 준비해야돼
maybe he plans something
a little more interesting
than hanging out at home,
watching TV.
'닥터후'라도?
Even Doctor Who?
'닥터후'라도
Even Doctor Who.
못 참겠다
SHELDON:
All right, that's it.
닥터후 컨벤션에서 빠져라
(snaps fingers)
Who Con-- you're out.
버그가 접수됐어
Okay, bug report taken.
다음 번에는 재밌는
데이트를 준비할게
Next time I will
have a better plan
for our evening's activity.
고마워,
내일 보자
Well, thank you.
I'll see you tomorrow.
잊을 뻔 했네
Oh, wait, here,
almost forgot.
여기
Here.
이건 뭐야?
What's this?
버그 보고서야
My bug report to you.
리스트가 꽤 길다
Well, that's quite
a list you got there.
중요도에 따라
색깔이 달라
It's color coded.
Oh.
빨간 색은
당장 고쳐야 하고
Uh, red means
"fix right away."
노랑은 시간 날때
Yellow is
"eh, whenever you
get a chance."
초록은
And green,
견딜만하다는 뜻이야
is "I could probably
learn to live with it."
아래에 적어뒀어
There's a key down
here at the bottom.
깔끔하지?
It's neat, huh?
(smacks lips)
그러네
Yep.
그럼 잘자
So, have a good night.
그래
(smacks lips)
Yep.
어때?
Look at that.
언젠가는 후손들에게
말할 날이 올 거야
Some day, we will tell
future generations
데이트가 어려웠던
시절은 지나갔다고
that dating used to be hard.
그 리스트에 쓸
내용이 있었어?
What's baffling me
is what you
could've possibly put
on the list.
너무 금발이다?
"Hair too golden"?
너무 예쁘게 웃는다?
"Laugh too musical"?
그녀의 존재로
세상이 더 아름답다?
"World too much a better place
for her mere presence in it"?
먹으면서 쉬지 않고
떠들어대는 건 어때?
How about "constantly talks
with food in her mouth"?
저렇게 사랑스러운 여자는
뭘 먹어도 이쁜 법이야
Her heart's full of love, no
one cares what's in her mouth.
시리, 잘 지내?
(chimes)
So, Siri, what's happening?
How are you?
잘 지내고 있습니다
(chimes)
I am well.
뭐하고 있어?
(chimes)
What are you doing right now?
뭐하고 있냐고요?
(chimes)
What am I doing?
당신과 얘기하고 있어요
I'm talking with you.
목소리가 정말 좋다
(chimes)
You have a beautiful voice.
칭찬해주셔서 감사합니다
(chimes) Thank you,
it's nice to be appreciated.
그렇겠지
I bet it is.
여자들은 왜
나를 싫어할까?
(chimes)
Why don't women like me?
확인해볼게요
(chimes)
Let me check on that.
'여자들은 왜 나를
싫어할까'로 검색할까요?
How about a Web search
for "Why don't women like me?"
됐어
No need.
이미 해봤어
I've already done that.
시리, 넌 성이 뭐야?
(chimes)
Siri, do you have a last name?
시리라고 합니다
(chimes)
My name is Siri.
그게 이름이구나
Ah, one name.
가수 셰어, 마돈나,
아델처럼
Like, uh, Cher,
Madonna, Adele.
날 미치게 하는 여자들이지
All the women who rock me.
내 이름은 라제쉬인데
그냥 라지라고 불러줘
(chimes) My name is Rajesh,
but you can call me Raj.
라지라고 불러드릴까요?
(chimes) Would you like me
to call you Raj?
섹시라고 부르면 더 좋지
(chimes) I'd like you
to call me sexy.
지금부터 섹시라고
부르겠습니다
(chimes)
From now on, I'll call you sexy.
좋습니까?
Okay?
좋아
Okay!
시리, 젤라토가 먹고 싶어
(chimes)
Siri, I'm in the mood for gelato.
젤라토를 판매하는
레스토랑이 10개 있습니다
(chimes) I found ten restaurants
whose reviews mention gelato.
그 중 7개가
근처에 있습니다
Seven of them
are fairly close to you.
고마워, 달링
(chimes)
Thank you, darling.
언제든지요, 섹시
(chimes) You are most certainly
welcome, sexy.
잘한다, 쿠트라팔리
Well done,
Dr. Koothrappali.
응?
I'm sorry?
엄청난 진화를 했군
You've taken a great
evolutionary leap
인간 접촉을 버리고
by abandoning human interaction
and allowing yourself
영혼 없는 기계와
로맨틱 관계를 갖다니
to romantically bond
with a soulless machine.
잘했어
Kudos.
관계라니
I haven't bonded with it.
아, 그렇지
Oh, no, of course.
이해해
I understand.
이 세상은 아직
그런 관계를 인정하지 않지
You're afraid the world
isn't ready for your taboo love.
비밀로 해줄게
Your secret's safe with me.
그냥 폰이야
It's just a phone.
쿠퍼
Cooper.
크립키
Kripke.
전할 말이 있어
Heads up.
로스만 교수가 소립자 물리
실험실에 또 오줌을 쌌어
Professor Rothman urinated in
the particle physics wab again,
은퇴 파티를 좀
앞당기려고
so we're going to move up
his wetirement party.
금요일 5시,
음식 준비해와
Fwiday, 5:00-- pot wuck.
고마워, 배리
Thanks, Barry.
시리, 금요일 아침에
빵을 만들어 놓으라고 알려줘
(chimes)
Siri, remind me
Friday morning
to make my famous popovers.
네, 그렇게 하겠습니다
(chimes)
All right, I'll remind you.
시리 구입했네?
You got Siwi, huh?
음성 인식
잘 안 되던데
Voice wecognition
on that thing is terrible.
이것 봐
Wook.
시리, 웨스토왕 좀
소개해 주세요
(chimes) Siwi, can you wecommend
a westauwant?
미안해요, 배위
(chimes)
SIRI: I'm sorry, Bawwy.
웨스토왕이 뭔지 모르겠네요
I don't understand
"wecommend a westauwant."
다시 들어봐
(chimes)
Wisten to me.
웨스토왕이 아니라
웨스토왕 말야
Not westauwant; westauwant.
웨스토왕이 아니라
웨스트왕이라니
(chimes)
I don't know what you mean
잘 모르겠습니다
by "not westauwant; westauwant."
봤어?
쓰레기야
See? Total cwap.
넌 못 쓰겠다, 시위
You suck, Siwi.
그렇게 대하지 마
Hey, don't talk to her
like that.
숙녀잖아
She's a lady.
어젯밤에 웹에 올릴
거시기 사진을 찍어준 숙녀다
Well, that wady
took high-wes pictures
of my junk wast night
for Cwaigswist.
이따 봐
Waiter.
들어와
PENNY:
It's open.
Hey.
준비됐어?
You ready to go?
잠시만
Yeah, hang on.
이 챕터만 읽고
Let me just finish this chapter.
나중에 읽으면 안돼?
Can you finish it later?
안돼
No, I can't.
독서는 내 삶의
중요한 부분이야
Reading books is a big part of
my life now because, you know,
그래야 너랑 더 깊은
대화를 나눌 수 있어
we'd have more fun things
to talk about if I read more.
좋아
Great. Good. Great.
뭘 읽는데?
What are you reading?
2주 안에 복근 만들기
Two Weeks to Rock Hard Abs.
제목 자체가 스포일러네,
안 그래?
They kind of spoil the ending
right in the name of that,
don't they?
알겠어
All right.
잘해보기로 했잖아
Look, just remember
how this works.
이런 거로 화낼 필요가 없어
We don't get mad
about these things.
전에 네가 말한
버그도 해결했어
Uh, speaking of which,
I've addressed
데이트 계획 짜는 거 말야
your bug report on
my date planning.
오늘은 재밌게 놀아보자
Got a really fun
evening for you.
서프라이즈를 준비했어
It's kind of a surprise.
그래, 좋아
All right. Terrific.
굽이 낮은 신발을
좀 찾아볼게
Well, let me just go find a pair
of shoes that aren't so tall.
네가 엄마랑 산책하러
나간 기분이 안 들게
We wouldn't want you
to feel like you were
out for a walk with your mommy.
고마워
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh.
이건 내가 작성한 리스트야
Here's my list
for you-- right there.
(clears throat)
그래, 그럴 수 있지
All right, fair enough.
더 조용하게 키스할 수 있어
I certainly can be quieter
when we kiss.
열정을 표현한 거였는데
I thought it was an expression
of passion,
네가 볼 때는
축축하고 이상하구나
but if it's coming across
as "juicy and weird,"
나도 그걸 원하진 않아
who wants that?
이건 무슨 소리지
Uh, uh... I'm sorry.
내 눈썹이 어째서
멍청해 보이지?
Can you be more specific
on how my eyebrows are "stupid"?
됐다,
여기 설명이 있네
Na, never mind.
It's right here.
딱 맞춰 왔네
Good timing.
저녁 거의 다 됐어
Dinner's almost ready.
잘됐다
Great.
냄새가 끝내주네
Oh, smells
amazing in here.
메뉴가 뭐야?
Oh, what are we eating?
이국적인 요리야
Oh, an exotic little treat.
시리랑 북경 오리
얘기를 하고 있었어
I was just talking to Siri
about Peking duck,
중국 슈퍼가 4개 있는데
and she said she knew
about four Chinese grocers,
그 중 2개가
근처에 있대
two of which were
fairly close to me.
나도 시리처럼
즉흥적으로 살려고
Her spontaneity
is contagious.
시리는 누구야?
Who's Siri?
여자친구 생겼어?
Is he dating somebody new?
응, 휴대폰이지
Yes. His phone.
Oh.
귀여운 건지
변태인 건지
Is that cute
or creepy?
Uh-huh.
와인 마실래?
Can I pour you
some wine?
좋아할 것 같아
I think you'll
enjoy it.
북경 오리를 먹을 때는
쇼비뇽 블랑을 주로 마시는데
The traditional
choice
with Peking duck
is a sauvignon blanc,
시리는 달콤한
리슬링을 추천했어
but Siri suggested
an off-dry Riesling.
난 확신이 안 갔지만
I wasn't sure,
마트에서 시리랑
다투고 싶지는 않았어
but I didn't want
to have an argument
with her in the middle
of Trader Joe's.
시리한테 뭘 입히면 좋을까?
Now, what should we
put Siri in for dinner?
호피, 반짝이?
Leopard, sparkles, or
아니면 코코 샤넬이
말한 것처럼
to paraphrase Coco Chanel,
언제나 고급스러워 보이는
블랙 케이스?
you can never go wrong
with a little black case?
시리, 재즈 음악 좀 부탁할게
(chimes)
Siri, play some smooth jazz.
재즈 곡을 재생 중입니다
(chimes)
Playing smooth jazz.
(Kenny G music playing)
이럴 수가, 케니 G
Oh, my God, Kenny G?!
이 여자는 나를
너무 잘 알아
This woman can read me
like a book.
내 소울메이트를
갤러리아에서 구입했다니
I can't believe
I bought my soul mate
at Glendale Galleria.
이제 그만 가볼까
(whispering): I don't know if
I want to stay.
(gunfire)
최고야
This is amazing.
이건 어떻게 준비했어?
How did you even get
this idea?
너네 아빠한테 전화했지
I called your dad.
어릴 때 뭘
좋아했는지 물어봤어
I asked him what things
you liked to do
when you were a kid.
소를 구해 오는 것보다는
이게 쉬워 보였어
This seemed easier
than getting a cow out here
so you could tip it.
넌 정말 최고야
Okay, you're kind of
really great.
나한테 목 마사지를 받으면
You mean for a person
whose neck massages
독수리한테 잡혀서 둥지로
끌려가고 있는 것 같다며?
feel like an eagle is trying
to carry you to its nest?
이것도 버그네
Okay, bug report.
방금 칭찬을 했잖아
I just complimented you.
그냥 받아들이고 조용히 해
You should take it and shut up.
그래, 미안
Right. Sorry, sorry.
계속 사과하지 마
And stop apologizing
all the time.
맞다, 미안해
Right. Sorry.
그냥 뭔가를 쏘자
All right,
let's shoot stuff.
어떻게 하는지 알려줄까?
You want me to show you
what to do?
난 'Grand Theft Auto'를
자주 하잖아
I play a lot of
Grand Theft Auto.
이 정도는 껌이지
I think I know how
to handle a gat.
터프한 척 하니까
좀 귀엽네
Wow. You are cute
when you get all gangsta.
(gunshot)
(yells)
Ooh!
(yelling)
(whining)
(panting)
나 총상 입었어
So, I've got a
gunshot wound.
좀 멋지지?
That's pretty
bad-ass.
리복 운동화가
총상을 입고
No, you've got a Reebok
with a gunshot wound
넌 새끼 발가락이
조금 까진 것 뿐이야
and an ouchie on your pinkie toe.
(laughs)
이봐, 난 반창고도 붙였어
Hello? They gave
me a Band-Aid.
병원에서는 아무때나
반창고를 붙여주지 않아
Hospitals do not
issue Band-Aids
unless it is
medically necessary.
그게 법이야
That is the law.
(laughs)
오늘 정말 즐거웠어
Well, thank you
for a really cool evening.
응급실에서 스타워즈
양말 숨겨줘서 고마워
Thank you for hiding
my Star Wars socks
at the emergency room.
(laughs)
베타 테스트가
어땠는지 평가해볼까?
Is it a good time to
evaluate the beta test
and see where we stand?
괜찮아 보이네
Things are looking good.
아직도 천천히 나가는 거야?
So, are we still
taking things slow?
오늘은 총상을 입고
Because a gunshot
wound today,
지난 주에는
서랍에 엄지가 끼었어
and last week, I slammed my
thumb in the kitchen drawer.
난 시간이
얼마 안 남았어
We don't know how
much time I have.
잘자
Good night, you.
(Bavarian music playing)
구텐탁, 유튜브
Guten Tag, das YouTube.
전 바이에른 사람입니다
Ich bin ein Bavarian.
저는 프레첼이에요
Und ich bin eine pretzel!
쉘든 쿠퍼와 함께
Und dis is Sheldon
Cooper Presents: Fun...
깃발 공부를 합시다
Mit...
Flags.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
왼쪽 첫번 째 문입니다
First door on the left.
감사합니다
Thank you.
(sighs)
데이브, 청소기 수리점
6개를 찾았습니다
Dave, I found six vacuum cleaner
repair shops in your area.
그 중 4개가
근처에 있습니다
Four are fairly close to you.
(clearing his throat)
안녕, 섹시
Hello, sexy.
어떻게 도와드릴까요?
What can I help you with?
사랑을 나누고 싶다면
말만 하세요
If you'd like to make
love to me, just tell me.
(guttural utterances)
죄송합니다,
무슨 말인지...
I'm sorry. I don't
understand...
(guttural utterances)
안돼!
No!